savevalet.com 2014-07-02

# SaveValet

1\. INTRODUCTION

1.1. PURPOSE. Save Valet, LLC ('us', 'we', 'Save Valet' or 'Company') respects the privacy rights of the users of the Company Website www.savevalet.com and any affiliated sites (the 'Site') and any services, applications, and software made available by Save Valet, LLC (collectively with the Site referred to as 'Services'). We make commercially reasonable efforts to abide by the following privacy principles for all the personally identifiable information we collect from you. Your use of any of the Save Valet Services serves as your consent to the collection, storage, manipulation, transfer, disclosure and any other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Your sole remedy, should you disagree with this Privacy Policy (either now or as it may be amended or modified in the future) is to cease using the Save Valet Services. 

1.2. NOTICE CONCERNING CHILDREN. PLEASE NOTE: We do not direct any of our content specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children's privacy online. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a Site user is under age 13, we will promptly delete any personal information in that user's account.

2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES

2.1. INFORMATION COLLECTED & USED (a) LOGIN DATA COLLECTED. We collect information regarding your use of the Save Valet Site and Services, and all details about your login (including but not limited to time and duration and last known login date and time). We also track and analyze non-personally identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from you and may provide such information to third parties at our sole option.

(b) CONTACT INFORMATION. In operating the Site and Services, Company may include registration, subscription accounts, online surveys, and other online forms that gives you and other users the opportunity to provide names, e-mail addresses, U.S. postal address and other contact information. In registering for the use of Services on this Site, you will provide information such as your name, username, password, email address, postal address and other contact information or other information requested at the time of registration. You acknowledge this information is personal to you and, by creating an Save Valet account, you allow Save Valet and others to identify you.

(c) PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED. In order for you to access certain Services that we offer via the Site, we require you to provide us with certain information that personally identifies you ('Personal Information'). Personal Information includes the following categories of information: (1) Contact Data (such as your name, mailing address, and e-mail address); (2) Financial Data (such as your account or credit card number); and (3) Demographic Data (such as your zip code, age, and income). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. You must provide contact information (such as name, email). We use this information to fill your order for a subscription to Save Valet products. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. When you subscribe to one of Save Valet products you will receive email from us. We do not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically provide this information on a voluntary basis. When and if you communicate with us by e-mail, complete online forms, surveys or contest entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.

(d) COMPARATIVE SHOPPING. Save Valet is designed to help you compare products and prices while you shop online. When you use your browser to search for products on certain websites, the Save Valet Extension will automatically check numerous other ecommerce sites to see if there are better prices available from other retailers (i.e. the same product at a lower price). Save Valet collects and receives some information from third party websites that you visit via a link provided by the Save Valet extension. This information includes pages that you visit at that website and information about whether you choose to purchase a product from that website. We also collect information on the url of the site you originally searched on; the characteristics of the product and the search terms (if any) you used to get there; the url of any site that you visited after being notified by the Save Valet Extension; anonymous technical and routing information relating to your product search and any visit that you make to a third party site after being alerted by the Save Valet Extension. 

(e) GEOGRAPHICAL INFORMATION. Save Valet may access your geographic location data at the time that you login to Save Valet Services. We may also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from you and provide such information to third parties.

2.2. WHAT ADDITIONAL INFORMATION DOES COMPANY COLLECT AND USE? (a) AUTOMATIC COLLECTION. Our servers automatically recognize visitors' domain names and IP addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet), cookie information, traffic data and other information you request. No personal information about you is revealed in this process. Save Valet may gather information about the number and frequency of visits to the Site and Services. The Site may also gather anonymous 'traffic data' that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. Except as otherwise provided, we do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

(b) COOKIES. We use cookies to make portions of the site work better by storing user preferences and trends. We send these small files to your computer. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse them. If you do this, some features of Save Valet may not work correctly. This data will be used in aggregate form; no specific users will be tracked. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.savevalet.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third party.

Our third party partners employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), images, and scripts that help them better manage content on our Site. We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers' or Users' personally identifiable information.

3\. USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION

3.1. WHAT DOES COMPANY DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION?

(a) PERSONAL & CONTACT INFORMATION. We use Contact Data to send you information about our company or our products or services, or promotional material from some of our Partners, or to contact you when necessary. We may use your personal information to verify your identity, to check your qualifications, or to follow up with transactions initiated on the Site. We may also use your contact information to send follow-up information regarding Save Valet's services, contact you regarding other services Save Valet offers, inform you of the availability of a newsletter or hotline information available on our site, any changes to the Site, or to send you additional information about Save Valet. We use your personal information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. We use this information to fill your order for a subscription to Save Valet products. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. When you subscribe to one of Save Valet products you will receive a welcome email. As part of registering for the Service, you may receive email newsletters from us. We do not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically provide this information on a voluntary basis. If you communicate with us by e-mail, complete online forms, surveys or contest entries, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information. If you do not want to receive promotional material or newsletters from us please follow the unsubscribe mechanism available in those messages or contact us at unsubscribe@savevalet.com

SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. We share certain categories of information we collect from you in the ways described in this Privacy Policy. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as sales, marketing and customer service (hereinafter 'Partners'). These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. We may use and share with our Partners the information including Contact Information or handles, geographic location and other information you provide to us to improve the Services we provide to you, notify you of changes or updates to our Services, customize your experience in using our Services and Site, customize any advertising and content you see on our Site or in using our Services, research the effectiveness of Services provided and adapt our Site and Services to our Customer's needs. We may share Demographic Data with Partners, advertisers and other third parties only on an aggregate basis. We may share Contact Data with other companies and Partners who may want to send you information about their products or services. We also share Contact Data and Financial Data with our Partners and business partners who assist us by performing core services (such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, or data storage and security) related to our operation of the Site. In addition, we maintain a procedure for you to request changes to your Personal Information; this procedure is described below.

(b) COMMUNICATION FROM THE SITE. We may communicate with you using information provided to us in various ways, which include but are not limited to:

Service-related Announcements We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

Customer Service Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your support inquiries, to provide some of the services you request. We will communicate with you by email.

Newsletters If you wish to subscribe to our newsletters, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe in each newsletter. Please see the 'unsubscribe' feature at the bottom of each newsletter or contact us at unsubscribe@savevalet.com. The customer's email list is stored on our system, but is not used by Save Valet in any other way other than to occasionally remind invited users to join the account that the account owner has registered for.

Surveys or Contests From time-to-time we may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information and demographic information (such as zip code). We use this information to notify contest winners and to monitor site traffic or personalize the site.

Testimonials We post testimonials from time to time. We always receive permission to post prior to posting.

Import Contacts You can import contacts from your Outlook or other email account address book to invite them to become members of our site. We collect the username and password for the email account you wish to import your contacts fro and will only use it for that purpose.

(c) LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES. This website may contact links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Save Valet. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website.

(d) LEGAL DISCLOSURE. We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

If Save Valet is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. (e) ACCESS TO INFORMATION. If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete it by making the change on the Account section page or by emailing our Customer Care at care@savevalet.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

(f) DATA RETENTION. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact our Customer Care at care@savevalet.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

(g) PUBLIC FORUMS. Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at care@savevalet.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. (h) SUPPLEMENTATION OF INFORMATION. In order to provide to enhance our services to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third party sources. To enrich our Profiles of individual customers, we tie this information to the personally identifiable information they have provided to us.

4\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY.

4.1. SECURITY. The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at privacy@savevalet.com.

5\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is required by law or in the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Save Valet or its parent company, subsidiaries or affiliates, (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Company or the users of the Site, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of the Site, or (d) enforce our Terms of Service.

6\. LOST OR STOLEN INFORMATION. You must promptly notify us if your credit card, user name, or password is lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that credit card number, user name, or password from your account and update our records accordingly.

7\. SOCIAL MEDIA FEATURES. Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the FaceBook button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

8\. CONTACT INFORMATION AND POLICY UPDATES 8.1. CONTACTING US. If you have any questions about this Policy, our practices related to this Site, or if you would like to have us remove your information from our database please feel free to contact us at the following:

Save Valet, LLC 1410 Second Street Suite 200 Santa Monica, CA 90401 privacy@savevalet.com

8.2. UPDATES AND CHANGES. We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
